live.
I say welcome brothers and sisters to
another Wednesday question and answer
where we open up with the 10
Commandments that God had written for
the whole world to keep. Brother James.
Yes, sir.
And God speak all these words saying, I
am the Lord thy God, which have brought
thee out of the land of Egypt, out of
the house of bondage. Thou shall have no
other gods before me. Thou shall not
make unto thee any graven image or any
likeness of anything that is in heaven
above or that is in the earth beneath or
that is in the water under the earth.
Thou shall not bow down thyself to them
nor serve them. For I the Lord thy God
am a jealous God, visiting the iniquity
of the fathers upon the children unto
the third and fourth generation of them
that hate me. And showing mercy unto
thousands of them that love me and keep
my commandments. Thou shall not take the
name of the Lord thy God in vain. For
the Lord will not hold him guiltless
that taketh his name in vain.
Remember the Sabbath day to keep it
holy. Six days shall thou labor and do
all thy work. But the seventh day is the
Sabbath of the Lord thy God. In it thou
shall not do any work. Thou nor thy son
nor thy daughter, thy man servant nor
thy maid servant nor thy cattle nor thy
stranger that is within thy gates. For
in six days the Lord made heaven and
earth, the sea and all that in them is
and rested the seventh day. Wherefore
the Lord blessed the Sabbath day and
hallowed it. Honor thy father and thy
mother that thy days may be long upon
the land which the Lord thy God giveth
thee. Thou shall not kill. Thou shall
not commit adultery. Thou shall not
steal. Thou shall not bear false witness
against thy neighbor. Thou shall not
covet thy neighbor's house. Thou shall
not covet thy neighbor's wife nor his
man servant nor his maid servant nor his
ox nor his ass nor anything that is thy
neighbor's. I read Exodus 20:1-17.
May the Lord add a blessing to the
reading of this word. In Jesus' name we
pray. Amen. Amen.
So here we're question and answer. You
can ask us a question and we'll answer
it according to the King James Bible.
And if we cannot find the answer, we
will seek further counsel to bring you
an answer at a later time.
The questions we will not answer are the
vague as well as the long scripture
questions and questions of debate. We're
not here to debate. We're here to spread
the true gospel of Jesus. So please be
as direct as possible with your
questions so we can be as direct as
possible with our answers out of the
King James Bible. No other Bibles or
books will be acknowledged on this
program. Also keep in mind that this is
a live stream so feel free to send in
your questions that pertain to
everlasting life. We just ask you that
you please keep them to a two scripture
maximum. But let me introduce you to
family that's on the panel this evening.
We got brother Jerome.
Grace and peace.
Brother Julius. Good evening, everybody.
Brother Dre.
Good evening.
Brother James. Good evening, everyone.
Sister Deborah.
Good evening.
And we have sister Casey as well as a
guest caller with us and I'm brother
Cornell. What is our first question of
the evening?
Uh yes, there are several held over
questions that will be answered first
before getting into tonight's Q&A.
Marquetta
Gay asks, at what point in an
individual's life are they accountable
for their actions?
All right. So at what time in someone's
life are they held accountable for their
actions? Brother Julius.
Let's go to Exodus the 30th chapter.
Brother James, Exodus the 30th chapter.
The age of a according to the word of
God.
You know, a man says uh when you begin
to understand right from wrong. Well,
let's look at what the Bible says. We're
talking about accountability.
Uh Exodus the 30th chapter and let's
read verse 12. This is what the Lord
said to Israel. Israel is the microcosm
of the world to the world. So goes
Israel, so goes the world. Exodus 30,
read verse 12. Go ahead, brother.
When thou takest the sum of the children
of Israel after their number,
then shall they give every man a ransom
for his soul unto the Lord.
When thou numberest them that there be
no plague among them when thou numberest
them. Skip down to verse 14 and read it.
Everyone that passeth among them that
are numbered from 20 years old and above
shall give an offering unto the Lord.
Now, let's go to Numbers the first
chapter.
Numbers the first chapter.
>> [clears throat]
>> And we're going to read
verse two and three.
Go ahead, brother. Okay.
Take ye the sum of all the congregation
of the children of Israel after their
families by the house of their fathers
with the number of their names, every
man by their polls.
From 20 years old and upward, all that
are able to go forth to war in Israel,
thou and Aaron shall number them by
their armies. So now, Israel was in the
wilderness and look what happened in the
wilderness when they sinned against God.
Numbers the 14th chapter.
And this is the out of the mouth of the
Lord to Moses. Numbers 14, when they
sinned against God, look what he said at
verse 29.
Your carcasses shall fall in this
wilderness. And all that were numbered
of you according to your whole number
from 20 years old and upward which have
murmured against me.
Verse 30.
Doubtless ye shall not come into the
land concerning which I swear to make
you dwell therein. Except only
save Caleb Caleb the son of Jephunneh
and Joshua the son of Nun.
But everybody them the only ones that
came through came out of the wilderness.
But everybody else 20 years old and
upward died.
That's all I got, brother Cornell.
Man says man says 18 for a girl, 21 for
a male. The Lord said 20 years old.
That's all I got.
All right.
We're going to leave it right there and
move on to our next question.
Moving on. Jade Enduring asks, is
someone with psoriasis or athlete's foot
considered unclean?
Uh it's just a condition you got.
You know,
um there's a lot of different conditions
out here that people can have, but
having psoriasis or athlete's foot is
not considered to put you in the unclean
category.
Anybody else got something they'd like
to add to that? Is there an issue? Plus,
blood is it bleeding?
Yeah, if it's not doing that, then you
know,
All right.
That's all we got on that as we move on
to our next question.
Our next question. Sky Rider says, if
the fourth trumpet brings about 1/3 of
the sun, moon, and stars being darkened
in Revelation 8, then how does the
fourth vial of wrath have the sun
scorching people in Revelation 16?
All right.
How does that, brother Jerome?
Well, let's um read the verses
and see what it actually says. Go to
Reve- let's do the Revelations 8 first
and read verse 12.
Okay. Revelation 8:12 says, And the
fourth angel sounded, and the third part
of the sun was smitten, and the third
part of the moon, and the third part of
the stars. So as the third part of them
was darkened, and the day shone not for
a third part of it, and the night
likewise.
Okay, so just wanted to take you there
to show where what verse
uh they were referring to about the
third part. Now, let's go to chapter 16
in Revelations
and read verse
8 and 9. Cuz that that will be the
fourth vial that's associated with the
fourth trumpet. Okay?
Revelation 16:8 and 9.
Okay. It says, And the fourth angel
poured out his vial upon the sun. And
power was given unto him to scorch men
with fire.
And men were scorched with great
And blasphemed the name of God, which
hath power over these plagues. And they
repented not to give him glory.
Okay, so to be honest with you,
the verse don't actually tell us how
it's being done. It's just telling you
it's being done, okay? And so,
uh
you just got to go by what the verse
says. You know, I can't add to it, I
can't take anything from it, you know.
Uh it don't tell us how, so I can't I
can't give you an answer how.
You know.
Uh that's all I got on it.
Right.
Sometimes that itself is an answer,
brother. Thank you for that.
All right, we're going to move on to our
next question.
Next question, Child of Israel asks, in
2 Corinthians 6:2,
is every day in the life you serve God a
day of salvation,
since willful sin isn't yield to?
All right, brother Dre, what about the 2
Corinthians and everyday life?
Let's let's go read that. Let's start at
verse 1. We'll read verse
1 and 2. Go ahead, brother.
Okay.
2 Corinthians 6:1-2 says,
We then, as workers together with him,
beseech you also that you receive not
the grace of God in vain.
Mhm. For he said, I have heard thee in a
time accepted. And in the day of
salvation have I secured thee.
Behold, now is the accepted time.
Behold, now is the day of salvation. So,
like in Hebrews and in Psalms, it tell
you when you hear his voice, harden not
your heart as in the day of provocation,
which they did that, but
uh skip down and read verse 4.
But in all things, approving ourselves
as the ministers of God, in much
patience, in afflictions, in
necessities, in distresses.
Okay, so this goes on to tell you how
you should serve God and how the
ministers should serve the Lord, but
that second verse is a direct quote
that's from Isaiah 49. Let's go there.
Isaiah 49. But it's simply telling us
that today, when you hear his voice, do
what he says, because life is short.
Yes, sir.
Isaiah 40 9:8.
Read it when you get there, brother.
Isaiah 49:8 says, Thus saith the Lord,
in an acceptable time have I heard thee.
And in a day of salvation have I helped
thee. And I will preserve thee and give
thee for a covenant of the people to
establish the earth, to cause it to I'm
sorry, to cause to inherit the desolate
heritages. So, if we hear him and we do
what he say, we will inherit the
desolate heritages
and those places that God promised us.
But it's a urgency in the moment. When
you hear his voice, harden not your
heart. One more place. Let's go to James
4 and read verse 14. James 4:14.
Read it when you get there, brother.
James 4:14 says, Whereas you know not
what shall be on the morrow. For what is
your life? It is even a vapor that
appeareth for a little time and then
vanishes away. That's right. So, read
13, too. Go ahead, brother.
Go to now, ye that say, today or
tomorrow we will go into such a city and
continue there a year and buy and sell
and get gain. And you don't know if you
going to make it to that city
because your life is a vapor.
You ain't promised tomorrow, so when you
hear his voice,
you do what he say.
That's all I got. Yep. Can we read that
verse 15, too, Dre, cuz I like how you
said how short life is. Yes, sir.
Verse 15. It says, For that ye ought to
say, if the Lord will, we shall live and
do this or that. That is right, brother.
Yep. Yep, very short indeed, brother,
but thank you for that. Hope that
answered their question as we move on to
our next one.
Next one, Kenya Hayes asks, is the Holy
Spirit a force that comes upon you or
dwells in you, etc.? I had an
interesting conversation with a Hebrew
Israelite, a Jehovah Witness, and a
Sunday church Christian. Please make it
plain.
All right. Like to have a lot of
conversation going on about the Holy
Spirit. Let's call her.
Well, you know, the answer to the
question
that comes upon you uh
uh
the spirit is a force that comes upon
you. No, it's not That's No, it's not.
First thing, you you have to know what
you're dealing with.
Um let's let's let's do a little
reading.
Let's go into uh
St. John, the 14th chapter.
And we're going to read verse 15 through
18.
Then we're going to skip to 26.
Okay.
St. John
14.
Let's see.
That was 14?
Yep. Uh-huh. Okay.
And
Verses 15 through 18, then we're going
to skip to 26. Okay.
John 14:15-18
says, If ye love me, keep my
commandments.
And I will pray the Father, and he shall
give you another Comforter,
that he may abide with you forever,
even the spirit of truth, whom the world
cannot receive, because it seeth him
not, neither knoweth him. But ye know
him, for he dwelleth with you and shall
be in you.
Now, we're going to we're going to we're
going to examine this, you know, but
this Comforter going to be in you
and it's going to be with you and in
you. But we're going to deal with that
in you
after a while. I need you to read verse
26 now. Okay. Do you want me to read 18
or jump to 26, sir?
Read 18. Read 18.
It says, I will not leave you
comfortless. I will come to you.
Now, verse 26 says, But the Comforter,
which is the Holy Ghost, whom the Father
will send in my name, he shall teach you
all things and bring all things to your
remembrance, whatsoever I have said unto
you.
See, now this Comforter, which is the
Holy Ghost, he he shall teach you all
things
and bring all things into your memory
which I have spoke to you.
So,
this Comforter is an informer. He come
to open your eyes.
Now, we're going to have a look at the
when he said he's going to be with you
and he's going to be in you.
When people read that, they think that
you got
this uh entity inside of you. No, you
got to remember, the Lord is not
speaking to no individual. He is
speaking into a group of all men. So,
let me show you what that in you really
means.
Let's go into Haggai,
the second chapter.
And we're going to read verse 1 through
12.
Okay, Haggai.
Zephaniah and then Haggai, that book
right before
Zechariah.
Okay.
And that was Haggai
2 1 through 5. Okay. It says,
In the seventh month, in the one and
twentieth day of the month, came the
word of the Lord by the prophet Haggai
saying,
Speak now to Zerubbabel, the son of
Shealtiel, governor of Judah, and to
Joshua, the son of Josedech, the high
priest, and to the residue of the people
saying,
Who is left among you that saw this
house in her first glory?
And how do you see it now?
Is it not in your eyes in comparison of
it as nothing?
No. What this what this this this house
is talking about the temple that Solomon
built.
Now, when they was they they went back
to rebuild the temple because they got
the orders from
Persian King Cyrus.
And when they built that temple compared
to the magnificent of Solomon's temple,
this was nothing in their eyes. But
still
the Lord let you know through the
prophet Haggai that this was something
to him. Go ahead and read. What did he
say?
Verse four says, "Yet now be strong, O
Zerubbabel, saith the Lord. And be
strong, O Joshua, son of Josedech, the
high priest.
And be strong
and be strong, all ye people of the
land, saith the Lord. And work, for I am
with you, saith the Lord of hosts.
According to the word that I covenanted
with you when you came out of Egypt, so
my spirit remaineth among you.
Fear ye not.
Do not he's telling them.
Be strong and go ahead and build this
temple.
You know, cuz my according to
the covenant I made with you when I
brought it to out of Egypt, my spirit is
still among you. Isn't that that's what
it's saying? Yes, sir.
You know, a lot of people and that's
what this my spirit is in you. So, let's
go and find you know, so so that in
means not inside of your body, that
means he's among you.
According to the same covenant I made
with you. So, now let's go back to
Exodus the 23rd chapter and look at this
spirit that was among them.
Exodus 23 and we're going to read verse
20 to 24.
Okay.
Exodus 23:20-24
says, "Behold, I send an angel before
thee
to keep thee in the way
and to bring thee into the place which I
have prepared.
Beware of him.
Mhm. He sent an angel before them to
keep them in the way.
Take them where he wanted them to be. Go
ahead and read.
Beware of him and obey his voice.
Provoke him not,
for he will not pardon your
transgressions, for my name is in him.
Do now. The There's no way Mhm. He's in
the Holy Spirit. His name was in that
angel.
He said, "Now beware of him.
Provoke him not.
Obey his voice, for my name is in him."
Was that the last the 24th verse? No,
that was 21. Verse 22 says,
"But if thou shalt indeed obey his voice
and do all that I speak, then I will be
an enemy unto thine enemies and an
adversary unto thine adversaries.
Verse 23 says, "For mine angel shall go
before thee and bring thee in unto the
Amorites and the Hittites and the
Perizzites and the Canaanites and the
Hivites and the Jebusites, and I will
cut them off.
Thou shalt not bow down to their gods
nor serve them nor do after their works,
but thou shalt utterly overthrow them
and quite break down their images.
And what verse is that? That was 24.
Okay. So, he says he sent an angel
before that's where he sent an angel
among them.
And he told them, "Look,
I want you to throw down their altars
and do everything else. You know, and
don't make no kind of league with them."
But let's see what Israel
did.
And what else is this angel called?
Let's go into Isaiah the 63rd chapter.
We're going to read verses 7 through 10.
Okay.
Isaiah 63:7-10
says,
"I will mention the lovingkindness of
the Lord and the praises of the Lord,
according to all that the Lord hath
bestowed on us
and the great goodness [clears throat]
toward the house of Israel, which he
hath bestowed on them according to his
mercies and according to the multitude
of his lovingkindness.
For he said, "Surely they are my people,
children that will not lie." So, he was
their savior.
In all their affliction, he was
afflicted and the angel of his presence
saved them.
In his love and in his pity, he redeemed
them and he bare them and carried them
all the days of old.
But they rebelled and vexed his Holy
Spirit, therefore he was turned to be
their enemy and he fought against them.
Do now. This is the angel of the Lord.
You know, the Lord said he sent him
before you know, he he he said his
spirit was still among them. And right
here he called the angel by his two
titles.
The thing of
he is he was a
a holy angel and he is a holy spirit. Do
now. So, he said
"I'm going to send him among among you.
Obey him.
Do what he say because if you don't he
will become an enemy to you to you."
But what they do?
They rebelled and they vexed his Holy
Spirit
and he turned against them. And let's
see what we were talking about. Let's go
into
Judges the second chapter.
Judges chapter two
and uh
we'll start reading at verse one.
Judges two
and
uh
verse one.
Okay.
Judges two and verse one says,
"And an angel of the Lord came up from
Gilgal to Bochim and said, "I made you
go up out of Egypt
and have brought you in unto the land
which I sware unto your fathers. And I
said, "I will never break my covenant
with you."
Now, this is an angel talking now. Keep
reading.
"And ye shall make no league with the
inhabitants of this land.
Ye shall throw down their altars, but ye
have not obeyed my voice. Why have ye
done this?"
See, that's what it said in Isaiah the
63rd chapter. Read it. They rebelled
and vexed his Holy Spirit. He said,
"Look, I brought you out of Egypt, but I
said I'll never break my covenant with
you.
But you have but but what happened is
you you don't
turn to these people and rebel. Why have
you done this? Go ahead.
"Wherefore I also said, "I will not
drive them out from before you, but they
shall be as thorns in your sides and
their gods shall be a snare unto you."
Go ahead.
"And it came to pass, when the angel of
the Lord spoke these words unto all the
children of Israel, that the people
lifted up their voice and wept.
Okay. So, this Holy Spirit
was a holy angel.
And that's the one that the Lord
uh put in you. When he said he put in
you, he is not not talking about putting
inside of you, he put among us as a
people. But rebelled.
Do now.
This this this angel brought a message.
And uh we rebelled against him and he
told and he only said us speak to us
what we have already been told by the
Lord.
Now, the only thing that go So, this
angel was among us. He's among us right
now.
And leading and guiding us in the all
truth.
Let's see if we uh
study in the word and take it the way it
is.
So, but what but he don't go inside of
you. That defies the laws of physics.
Angels are physical beings.
Now,
there is something that goes inside of
you.
And that is the word of God. Let's have
a look at it.
You like
uh we're going to start in the Saint
John the sixth chapter
and we're going to read from
50 uh
uh
four to 56. Then we're going to skip.
Saint John six 4 to 56.
Okay. Saint John 6:54-56
say,
"Whoso eateth my flesh and drinketh my
blood hath eternal life, and I will
raise him up at the last day.
Uh-huh.
For my flesh is meat indeed and my blood
is drink indeed.
He that eateth my flesh and drinketh my
blood dwelleth in me and I in him."
Now,
that defies the laws of physics. How can
you dwell in the Lord and the Lord is
dwelling in you all at the same time?
Do now.
Was that was verse 56? Yes, sir.
Do not, what happened is
he said if you eat my flesh and drink my
blood,
you going to get eternal life. I'm going
to dwell in you and you in me.
But that was a hard saying and the and
his own disciples
was murmuring about it. Skip down to
verse 60 and and read verse 60 and 61.
It says, "Many therefore of his
disciples, when they had heard this,
said, 'This is a hard saying. Who can
hear it?'"
"When Jesus knew in himself that his
disciples murmured at it, he said unto
them, 'Does this offend you?'"
Does this offend you? Skip down to verse
63. He's going to jump plain now.
He said it is it is the spirit that
quickeneth.
The flesh profiteth nothing.
The words that I speak unto you, they
are spirit and they are life.
So it's the words he's telling you eat.
That's what he wants you to consume.
He's not going He's not He said he's
going to be in you and you going to be
in him. I mean, he's not going to go
inside of you, neither is the angel
going to go inside. The words that he
speak
and the words that he sent by the angel,
that is what's going to go inside of
you.
Now let's go into
Jeremiah 15th chapter. This is the last
place.
And we're going to read verses 15 and
16.
Okay.
Jeremiah 15:15
and 16 say,
"O Lord, thou knowest. Remember me and
visit me and revenge me of my
persecutors.
Take me not away in thy long-suffering.
Know that for thy sake I have suffered
rebuke."
"Thy words were found and I did eat
them."
"And the Mhm.
This is the verse.
"And thy word was unto me the joy and
rejoicing of my heart, for I am called
by thy name, O Lord God of hosts."
Now, how do you eat
the word of God?
By reading the book or somebody teaching
it to you.
So that's the only thing that goes into
you. Like I tell you in Revelation,
third chapter, I think about three in
the last couple of verses, it said, "I
stand at the door and knock. If you open
up to me, I'll come in and sup with you
and you with me." So he's talking about
the word. That's what enter you.
But as far as the Holy Spirit,
that
that informs you, that's merely a holy
angel.
So don't nothing come up on you with
force. I can see these people jumping
all down and kicking and slobbering all
out of their mouth. That's nothing but
theatrics. It's got nothing to do with
the word of God.
That's all I have to say.
All right. Hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next one.
Next one, Skywriter asks, "Are the
strangers in 2 Chronicles 1:5-9
talking about Israelites?"
Was it Is it 2 Chronicles 15?
Yes, it is. Again, in 2 Chronicles 15:9.
Verse nine.
Yes, talking about Israelites. All
right. Let's go there, James. Okay.
>> Read that verse and they want to know if
this is Israelites and the guest caller
will take it from there.
Okay. 2 Chronicles 15:9 says, "And he
gathered all Judah and Benjamin and the
strangers with them out of Ephraim and
Manasseh and out of Simeon, for they
fell to him out of Israel in abundance
when they saw that the Lord his God was
with him."
So these strangers is No, no, they're
not Israelites. Strangers have always
been among Israel.
And we always
Let's go into Exodus the 12th chapter
and and bring them out of and when
Israel come out of Egypt. Exodus 12:37
and 38.
Okay. Exodus 12:37 and 38 says, "And the
children of Israel journeyed from
Rameses to Succoth about 600,000
on foot that were men beside children."
"And a mixed multitude went up also with
them and flocks and herds, even very
much cattle."
Okay, that mixed multitude that went
among them was strangers.
And when the Lord take Israel back, the
stranger will still be there. Let's go
into Ezekiel.
The 47th chapter.
And we're going to read verses 21 to 23.
Okay. Ezekiel 47:21-23
says, "So shall ye divide this land unto
you according to the tribes of Israel.
And it shall come to pass that ye shall
divide it by lot for an inheritance unto
you and to the strangers that sojourn
among you,
which shall be got children among you.
And they shall be unto you as born in
the country among the children of
Israel. They shall have inheritance with
you among the tribes of Israel.
And it shall come to pass that in what
tribe the stranger sojourneth, there
shall ye give him his his inheritance,
saith the Lord God."
So now, when they come out of Egypt,
stranger was among us. And when the Lord
return Israel back after Jesus return
and put us back in our own land,
strangers are going to still be among us
and we're going to have to give them an
inheritance. So no, they weren't
Israelites, they were strangers like the
book said. That's all I have to say.
All right. Thank you for that. As we
move on to our next question.
Next question, Pray Brad wants help in
understanding Revelation 13:18.
She says, "A friend of mine thinks one
of the six represents us, human beings."
All right, Brother Julius, shed some
light.
Go to Revelation the 13th chapter,
James.
Because if one of the six represents us,
human beings, what do the other two
sixes represent?
Let's look at what the book say.
Revelation, let's read her verse. 13 and
read verse 18, James. When you get it,
go ahead.
"Here is wisdom. Let him that hath
understanding count the number of the
beast,
for it is the number of a man and his
number is 666."
Now,
notice notice what it says. It said
nothing about us. It is the number of a
man
and the number assigned to this man to
identify him is 666. Let's go to
Revelation back up to read Let's read
verse one. Let's go through this real
quick, James. Revelation
one.
Revelation one.
>> But Revelation 13:1. Go ahead, I'm
sorry. 13:1. Go ahead.
"And I stood upon the sand of the sea
and saw a beast rise up out of the sea
having seven heads and 10 horns. And I
saw
>> in the This is what John saw in the
future. Go ahead. "And upon his horns 10
crowns and upon his heads the name of
blasphemy." Uh-huh. "And the beast which
I saw was like unto a leopard and his
feet were as the feet of a bear and his
mouth as the mouth of a lion and the
dragon gave him his power and his seat
and great authority." These are the
Gentile four Gentile world ruling
nations that were that run and have
ruled the whole world and now we're in
the last one which is the Romans, okay?
And the Romans the head of the Roman uh
religion is the Pope. This is the number
of a man. Notice So now,
skip down to verse six and go ahead.
Notice Notice he's using the personal
pronoun "his." Go ahead.
"And he opened his mouth and blasphemy
against God to blaspheme his name and
his tabernacle and them that dwell in
heaven."
And he got the power and the dragon gave
him his seat, his power and great
uh
authority. Skip down to verse 11. Same
thing. Go ahead. Now, our day and time.
Go ahead.
"And I beheld another beast coming up
out of the earth and he had two horns
like a lamb and he spake as a dragon."
So he looks godly, he sounds godly
because the lamb
uh represents Jesus, but it he's a false
prophet. This is This is a man. This is
This is why we said this is a man. Skip
down all the way down uh to verse 16 cuz
this is coming. This is what we're
waiting on. Go ahead.
"And he had power to give life unto the
image of the beast that the image of the
beast should both speak and cause that
as many as would not worship the image
of the beast should be killed. Go ahead.
And he causes all both small and great,
rich and poor, free and bond to receive
a mark in their right hand or in their
foreheads. Go ahead.
And that no man might buy or sell save
he that had the mark or the name of the
beast or
>> Or the name of the beast or what? the
number of his name.
Because it's number. Now read 18 cuz
this is a sign to a
really the head of the Roman church, the
Pope.
Whoever he be that feels this world. Go
ahead.
Here is wisdom. Let him that hath
understanding count the number of the
beast.
For it is the number of a man.
And his number is 600 three score and
six. So then when you break that number
down in Roman numerals and Roman
letters, it represents the Roman title
Vicarius Filii Dei, the substitute or
the replacement of the son of God.
And that's what the Pope is
looked upon as. The Roman Catholic
Church denies this, but it is evident
all over the book. Even give you the
colors of it. So this is the number of a
man. Did anybody want to add to that?
Don't get that mark.
Do not take that mark. That's the
number, but
the mark whatever the mark be, but that
this identifies
and assign number to
a man who would be the religious head of
the Catholic Church.
All right. Thank you for that. Hopefully
that answered their question as we move
on.
Moving on. Skywriter asks, "Did Paul
really write the book of Romans?" And
they gave Romans 16:22.
All right. Did Paul really write the
book of Romans, Brother Drake?
Let's go read that Romans 16:22.
Read it when you get it, Brother James.
Romans 16:22
says,
"I Tertius, Tertius, who wrote this
epistle, salute you in the Lord."
Yeah, so Tertius
is
Paul's scribe.
Paul is the author of the book of
Romans, but he used Tertius to do the
physical writing.
He was Paul's scribe and he wrote it.
Paul dictated it and he wrote it. That's
all I got.
Yeah. All right. Can I
Can I throw in a couple of scriptures?
Go ahead. I'm throwing in a couple
passages to make sure because uh
I want them to understand that
everything in this Bible was written by
a Hebrew Israelite. That's right.
>> had a scribe. Plus Paul had a problem.
It's obvious it was a vision a vision
problem.
And so I'mma show you.
He said, "First, let's go to 1
Corinthians 16th chapter and read verse
21."
1 Corinthians 16
and verse 20 1 Corinthians 16:21 says,
"The salutation of me, Paul, with mine
own hand."
It let you know that he wrote with his
own hand. Go to Galatians 6 and 11.
Some of it he wrote himself, but Paul
had a problem. Galatians 6 and 11.
Okay.
Galatians 6 and 11 says, "Ye see how
large a letter I have written unto you
with mine own hand."
Now, the large of letter he writ with
you in his own hand. Why was he
boasting?
Because he had a problem.
And let's take a quick look
and and see what that problem
is.
Go to Galatians the fourth chapter
and read verses
13 through 15.
Okay.
Galatians 4:13-15
says,
"Ye know how through infirmity of the
flesh I preached the gospel unto you at
the first.
And my temptation, which was in my
flesh, ye despised not.
Nor rejected, but received me as an
angel of God, even as Christ Jesus.
Where is then the blessedness ye spake
of? For I bear you record that if it had
been possible, ye would have plucked out
your own eyes and have given them to
me."
So now, Paul had a vision problem. He
had sought the Lord three times for it
and the Lord said he ain't going to do
it.
But still like uh Brother Drake said,
Israelites had
scribes. The scribe That was a That was
an occupation, scribe. But Paul wrote
some of his own stuff. But he had
scribes, too. To give you an example
about uh uh uh
about them having scribes,
we're going to go back and we're going
to look at uh
Jeremiah
36th chapter.
Read verses 14
17 through 18
and verse 32.
Okay.
Jeremiah 4 36:14
says,
"Therefore
36 and 4.
Oh, 36 and 4. Okay. Jeremiah 36:4 says,
"Then Jeremiah called Baruch the son of
Neriah, and Baruch wrote from the mouth
of Jeremiah all the words of the Lord
which he had spoken unto him upon a roll
of a book."
Skip down to verse 17 and 18.
And they asked Baruch, saying, "Tell us
now, how didst thou write all these
words at his mouth?"
Then Baruch answered them, "He
pronounced all these words unto me with
his mouth, and I wrote them with ink in
the book."
Mhm.
And skip down and read verse 32.
Then took Jeremiah another roll and gave
it to Baruch the scribe,
the son of Neriah, who wrote therein
from the mouth of Jeremiah all the words
of the book which Jehoiakim, king of
Judah, had burned in the fire. And there
were added besides unto them many like
words.
So now,
like Brother Drake said, Israel had
scribes.
But Paul wrote some of his stuff. He
probably would wrote more, but he had an
eye problem.
So now, look at the book of Jeremiah. Is
that called the book of Jeremiah and
Baruch?
No, sir.
Jeremiah. So all of Paul's writing
is all dictated by Paul.
That's all I wanted to add to that.
All right. Thank you for that, brother.
Hopefully that answered your question as
we move on to our next.
Moving on. Britt Brett asks, "Are there
any scriptures that I can share with my
family to inform them about
reincarnation?
They use that saying, 'They've been
here. They have been here before.' I
tell them that's not true. They're just
wise people."
All right. Brother Julius dealing with
reincarnation.
The word reincarnation is not written in
the KJV.
They've been watching too much
television.
Let's go and let's look at 1 Corinthians
the 15th chapter. They talking about
they've been here before. That That's
impossible.
We're going to show you why. 1
Corinthians the 15th chapter. When you
get it, Brother James, let's read 20
through 23.
Okay.
>> what the what what Paul said about
Jesus.
1 Corinthians
The only one that's been here before is
Jesus.
1 Corinthians 15:20 through 23. Go
ahead, brother.
But now is Christ risen from the dead
and become the firstfruits of them that
slept. So he came and resurrected lived
and resurrected. He's been here before.
Go ahead.
For since by man came death, by man came
also the resurrection of the dead.
Uh-huh. For as in Adam all die,
even so in Christ shall all be made
alive.
When, brother? Read. But every man in
his own order.
Christ the firstfruits,
afterward they that are Christ at his
coming. So you tell your loved ones
Christ ain't came, so that means they
ain't been here before.
So let's go to 1 Timothy the sixth
chapter.
1 Timothy the sixth chapter, Brother
James.
That is science Scientology and all that
kind of stuff.
And we going to pick this up at verse
14. Read verse 14.
And then we going to read verse 16.
Okay.
1 Timothy 6 verse 14 says, that thou
keep this commandment without spot.
Yeah. Unrebukable.
Until the appearing of our Lord Jesus
Christ. Notice nothing happened until
the Lord appears.
Go ahead, brother.
Verse 16 says, who only have immortality
dwelling in the light which no man can
approach unto.
You see?
You you see who only have immortality.
Go ahead.
Whom no man has seen
nor can see.
To whom be honor and power everlasting.
Amen.
That's all I got.
So,
no such thing as reincarnation. It is
called a resurrection.
The Bible teaches the resurrection just
like 1 Corinthians 15 chapter say, this
mortal must put on immortality. If they
been here before, they would have to be
immortals.
That's all I got.
All right, guest caller.
Let me throw a couple in. Go to St. John
the 6th
St. John the 6th chapter
and read verse 35
and then we going to skip down
Okay.
>> from 38 to 40.
1 John 6 and verse 35 says
St. John. St. John, right.
St. John verse 6 verse I mean, I'm
sorry, chapter 6 verse 35 says
And Jesus said unto them
I am the bread of life.
He that cometh to me shall never hunger
and he that believeth on me shall never
thirst.
38.
For I can
For I came down from heaven not to do
mine own will but the will of him that
sent me.
And this is the will of the And this is
the Father's will which has sent me that
all of all which he has given me I
should lose nothing but should raise it
up again at the last day.
Is the last day here?
No.
>> No.
You read.
Verse 40. And this is the will of him
that sent me.
That everyone which see it the son and
believeth on him may have everlasting
life and I will raise him up at the last
day.
Read it again. Read verse 44.
No man can come to me except the Father
which has sent me draw him. And I will
raise him up at the last day.
Read it one more time.
Read verse 54.
Whosoever eateth my flesh and drinketh
my blood hath eternal life and I will
raise him up at the last day.
So now, if your people
say they've been reincarnated, they are
calling Jesus a lie.
And he just told you four times
that ain't nobody coming out that ground
until the last day and the last day is
not here.
That's all I got to say.
Thank you.
>> All right.
Hope that answered your question as we
move on with the time check.
Yes, the time is 8:23.
Uh Skywriter asked, what does
it mean that money answers all things in
Ecclesiastes
10 verse 19?
All right, Jerome. Money answers all
things.
Let's go read it. Ecclesiastes chapter
10 verse 19.
Okay.
Ecclesiastes 10 verse 19 says, a feast
is made for laughter
and wine maketh merry.
But money answereth all things.
I just want to mention a few things that
kind of
um shine a little light on when you say
all things. Let's point out a few things
that money can't help with.
We got a lot of rich people out here
that wish that they money
could heal them of dire sicknesses.
And they they spend all kind of money
and and the Lord don't deliver them from
a lot of the sicknesses that they have.
Not just rich people. I'm just using
rich people for an example that have
plenty money.
Okay? And then you got a
a
a few verses I want to
read.
Um can we read
um
Ecclesiastes chapter 7 and then we going
to go to Psalms 49 after that. Let's
read that Ecclesiastes chapter 7. You
know, you you have benefits for money,
of course, you know?
It's obvious that there are benefits but
it's but there's certain things that
money can't help. Okay?
Ecclesiastes 7 and 12.
Okay. It says
for wisdom is a defense and money is a
defense.
But the excellency of knowledge is that
wisdom giveth life to them that have it.
Yeah. All right. So, it say money is a
defense but like I just pointed out but
there's certain things money can't help.
Okay? So, let's look at one more thing
and that'll be it. Let's go to Psalms
49.
And we going to read read verse 7
through 10.
Okay.
Psalm 49 verses 7 through 10 says
None of them can by any means redeem his
brother nor give to God a ransom for
him. Okay, how much money you got? You
can't give a ransom to deliver
yourself or anybody else
from death.
Go ahead.
For the redemption of their soul is
precious and it ceases forever.
That he should still live forever and
not see corruption.
For he seeth that wise men die.
Likewise, the fool and the brutish
person perish
and leave their wealth to others. Yeah.
That's all I got. Anybody want to add
that can.
And the love of money will get you in
trouble, too.
Can can we go to one Let's go to Acts 8
and just read one more thing here. Acts
and pick it up at verse 18.
Okay.
Acts 8
and 18.
Acts 8 and 18 says
And when Simon saw that through laying
on of the apostles' hands the Holy Ghost
was given, he offered them money. Go
ahead.
Saying, give me also this power that on
whosoever I lay hands, he may receive
the Holy Ghost. Go ahead.
But Peter said unto him
Thy money perish with thee.
Because thou has thought that the gift
of God may be purchased with money.
Can't money can't buy No.
Not at all.
No.
And that that 1 Timothy 6
and verse 10.
Brother James, right quick. Okay.
1 Timothy 6 and verse 10
It says
For the love of money is the root of all
evil.
Which while some coveted coveted after,
they have erred from the faith.
And pierced themselves through with many
sorrows.
Yep.
Yep. All right.
All right.
I hope that that answered your question
as we move on to our next one.
Moving on. Charlotte T says, Sunday
Christian says, the Holy Ghost is the
third part of the Trinity. I have also
heard the Holy Ghost is an angel.
Which is true and where can I find it in
scripture?
All right, guest caller. Here we got us
a Trinity question.
Yeah, well, you know
when it comes to the Trinity that we
talking
an angel. People talking about God the
Father, God the Son and God the Holy
Ghost. You cannot read that in the
Bible.
You can read
Father and God the Son.
Like in St. John, in the beginning was
the word. The word was God and the word
was God.
It was in the beginning with God. So,
the word was Jesus. But
first thing here is we got to find out
what angels are. Let's go into Hebrews.
First chapter.
We going to read verse 6 through 7 and
skip down to verse 14.
Okay.
Hebrews 1 verses 6 through 7 says,
"And again, when he bringeth in the
first begotten into the world, he saith,
And let all the angels of God worship
him."
"And of the angels he saith, Who maketh
his angels spirits, and his ministers a
flame of fire."
So, he makes his angels spirits. All the
angels are spirits. They're and they're
serving spirits.
Give me now the verse 14 and read
14 and read it.
14 says, "Are they not all ministering
spirits sent forth to minister for them
who shall be heirs of salvation?"
Oh, so all the angels are spirits, even
the evil angels.
But the one that uh uh that did not
follow Satan, let's let's see what they
are called. Let's go into Matthew the
25th chapter and read verse 31.
Matthew 25 and verse 31 says,
"When the Son of man shall come in his
glory, and all the holy angels with him,
then shall he sit upon the throne of his
glory."
Now, if they are holy
and they are spirit,
don't that make them holy spirits? Yep.
>> Yep. Yes, sir.
Angels. Do now, let's look at this
trinity.
Let's go into 1 John 5 and 7 and read
that where people get this from.
Okay.
>> 1 John 5 and 7.
It says,
"For there are three that bear record in
heaven,
the Father,
the Word, and the Holy Ghost, and these
three are one."
Okay. Well, let's we going pursue these
three right quick.
So, let's go in the Revelations.
First chapter
and have a look at it.
Okay.
Revelation 1
Chapter 1 and read verse 1 and 2.
Okay.
It says, "The revelation of Jesus
Christ,
which God
Okay, go ahead. which God
gave unto him to show unto his servants
things which must shortly come to pass.
And he sent
Who? To.
Go ahead, read it.
And he sent and signified it by his
angel
unto his servant John,
who bear
who bear record of the word of God, and
of the testimony of Jesus Christ, and of
all things that he saw."
So, the angel is three, isn't it?
Correct.
>> he gave it to John, then there was three
that bear record in heaven and one that
bore record in the earth. Isn't that
correct? Yep.
>> Correct. So, you got it.
You got the Father, which is God. You
got Son, which is God. You got the
angel, which is a serving spirit.
And let's go and look at him. He going
to call him another way.
This way he called the Father, the Son,
and the angel.
And let's see what else is
And let's you look at another way
the same
three is brought to you. Let's go into
St. John the 16th chapter.
Read verses 12 through 15.
Yes, sir.
Okay.
It's It says, "John
16 verse 12 says,
I have yet many things to say unto you,
but you cannot bear them now.
Howbeit, when he, the Spirit of truth,
is come, he will guide you into all
truth.
For he shall not
It's one, isn't it?
Correct.
Go ahead.
For he shall not speak of himself, but
whatsoever he shall hear, that speak
that shall he speak. And he will show
you things to come.
He shall glorify me, for he shall
receive of mine, and shall show it unto
you."
But where did he get it from?
Jesus.
>> it from Jesus. That's two, isn't
Correct.
>> Yeah, go ahead.
"All things that the Father hath are
mine.
Therefore said I that he shall take of
mine, and shall show it unto you."
So, now, so what then? Jesus got it from
the Father, didn't he?
Correct.
All things that the Father have are
mine. So, you got your three there. You
got your God the Father, you got God the
Son, and you got the Holy Spirit, which
in this case is an angel.
Now, let's run a few things real quick,
and I'm going to put an end to this. Go
into Revelation second chapter.
Read 1 and 2.
Verse and then we're going to skip.
Revelation 2
1 and 2.
Okay.
It says, "Unto the angel of the church
of Ephesus write, These things saith he
that holdeth the seven stars in his
right hand, who walketh in the midst of
the seven golden candlesticks.
I know thy works.
Mhm.
I know thy works and thy labor and thy
patience, and how thou canst not bear
them which are evil. And thou has tried
them which say they are apostles and are
not, and has found them liars."
Now,
when
when the when the message was finished,
then
it ended. Let me tell you how it ended.
Skip down to verse 7, verse 7.
And read it.
"He that hath an ear, let him hear what
the Spirit saith unto the churches.
To him that over
Now, when he got through reading, the
church of Ephesus, he didn't have an
ear, let him hear what the Spirit said
to the churches.
Then he went to another church.
And then he told gave them a message.
And let's see how it ended. Read verse
11.
"He that hath an ear, let him hear what
the Spirit saith unto the churches.
He that Mhm. Now, once he finished that
message, he went to another church. And
let's see how it ended.
Verse 17.
"He that hath an ear, let him hear what
the Spirit saith unto the churches.
There's the verse.
To him that overcometh will I give to
eat of the hidden manna, and will give
him a white stone, and in the stone a
new name written, which no man knoweth
saving he that receiveth it."
Now, all seven churches it ended up, He
that have an ear, let him hear what the
Spirit said unto the churches. So, the
Spirit is talking to the churches. Isn't
that what we saying here?
Yeah.
So, go to one last place. Revelation 12
and 16.
Okay. Revelation Revelation 12 and 16
says,
"And
and the and the earth helped the woman,
and the earth opened her
I'm sorry. Revelation 22 and 16. I'm
sorry. 22 No problem.
22 and 16 says,
"I Jesus, have sent my angel to testify
unto you these things in the churches.
I am the root and the offspring of
David, and the bright and morning star."
So, now, Jesus is the one that sent the
Spirit to all seven churches.
That's why I say, He that have an ear,
let him hear what the Spirit said to the
churches. Right here he said, And I
Jesus have sent mine angel to testify to
the churches.
So, you got your three. You got the
Father,
you got the Son, and you got the angel,
which is a spirit, a ministering spirit.
There is no such thing as God the
Father.
That's all I have to say.
>> God the Holy Ghost. God the Holy Ghost.
God the Holy Ghost.
No such thing.
That's all I have to say. Yep. All
right. Hope that answered your question
as we move on to our next one.
Next one, calmly says, "I know January
the 1st is not our New Year's, but is it
okay to stand outside and watch the
fireworks?"
Yes, Carla.
Why not?
Mhm.
There ain't nothing in the book against
Yep.
Yep. Just Just be careful. It's not only
fireworks, it'd be gunfire out there,
too. So, be careful.
All right. Hope that answered your
question our next one.
Next one, Linda Lynn asks, "Is it okay
to drop someone off somewhere so they
may attend a Sunday church?"
All right.
Dropping someone off
at a Sunday church. Yes, caller.
I don't know.
Whether it's okay or not, I can't answer
that. I don't have no book for it.
All right. We're going to move on to our
next one.
Next one, Skywriter asks, "What does it
mean that the power of God overshadowed
Mary in Luke 1:5 35?"
What is this power of God that
overshared overshadowed Mary in Luke
1:35, Brother Julius?
That is
the angel that's going to bring
the body and plant it inside of Mary.
Let's go to that Let's go to the
scripture read it. Luke 1
Luke 1 and pick it up at verse 26.
Can you read down to it quickly?
And the sixth month, the angel Gabriel
was sent from God unto a city of Galilee
named Nazareth. Yes, caller, just showed
you that this angel here, who who is
named Gabriel, is sent by God, a
ministering spirit, the Holy Ghost. Go
ahead.
To a virgin espoused to a man whose name
was Joseph of the house of David, and
the virgin's name was Mary. And what was
the message there in verse 30? Go ahead.
And the angel said unto her, "Fear not,
Mary, for thou hast found favor with
God."
Go ahead, 31. And behold, thou shalt
conceive in thy womb and bring forth a
son and shalt call his name Jesus. Go
ahead. He shall be great and shall be
called the son of the highest. Go ahead.
>> And the Lord And the Lord God shall give
unto him the throne of his father David.
Oh, go ahead. And he shall reign over
the house of Jacob forever, and of his
kingdom there shall be no end. Now, pay
attention to how it's going to happen.
Cuz look at what Mary said.
Had nothing to do with a flesh and blood
man. Go ahead. Then said Mary unto the
angel, "How shall this be, seeing I know
not a man?"
How shall this be?
I'm a virgin. I ain't I ain't never laid
with no man. Go ahead. And the angel
answered and said unto her, "The Holy
Ghost shall come upon thee.
And the power of the highest shall
overshadow thee. Therefore, also that
holy thing which shall be born of thee
shall be called the son of God." Now,
people think that angels lay with women.
No.
Angels do not reproduce. They are
messengers, ministering spirits. The
Holy Ghost shall come upon thee. The
They're going to come and he's going to
bring the body of Jesus
from heaven and put it and place it
inside of Mary's womb.
Let's go to Hebrews chapter 2.
Hebrews chapter 2.
That's why Mary said, "How shall this
be, seeing that I know not a man?"
Jesus
created man.
Man sinned. And so he had to come and
save this man.
2:14.
Hebrews 2:14. How is he going to do it?
Go ahead.
For as much then as the children are
partakers of flesh and blood, he also
himself likewise took part of the same.
Uh-huh. That through death he might
destroy him that had the power of death,
that is the devil. So, Jesus needed a
flesh and blood body, and that body was
prepared
in heaven. That's why he kept telling
you. Let's go to Hebrews the 10th
chapter.
Hebrews the 10th chapter.
And we're going to read verse 5. Hebrews
10:5.
It had to happen this way.
Go ahead.
Wherefore, when he cometh into the
world, he saith, "Sacrifice and offering
thou wouldest not, but a body hast thou
prepared me." So, there was a prepared
body that the angel brought from heaven
and placed it in Mary's womb. Let's go
to Psalm 139.
It was already prophesied.
Psalm 139, James, and let's pick this up
at verse 13 and 14.
Psalm 139
14 and 15. Look what David wrote about.
Go ahead.
I will praise thee, for I'm fearfully
and wonderfully made. Yes. Marvelous are
thy works. Yes. And that my soul knoweth
right well. Go ahead. My substance was
not hid from thee.
When I was made in secret and curiously
curiously wrought in the lower parts of
the earth. That's where he came in the
flesh, sister and brother. That body was
put inside of Mary. My last place, John,
the first chapter. Saint John, the first
chapter.
And we're going to read verse 1 and then
we going to skip.
That's why the book said, "Who have
believed our report?" People don't
believe. I believe. You know why? Cuz he
made me out of dirt.
Saint John 1:1. Go ahead.
In the beginning was the word. And the
word was with God, and the word was God.
Get down to 12 and we're going to go to
14. Go ahead.
But as many as received him, to them
gave he power to become the sons of God,
even to them that believe on his name.
Pay attention to this next verse. Go
ahead.
And the word was made Verse 13. Verse
13. Verse 13.
Which were born not of blood nor of the
will of the flesh, Uh-huh.
>> nor of the will of man, but of God. By
the power of God, sisters and brothers.
Go ahead.
And the word was made flesh and dwelt
among us. And we begat And we beheld his
glory, the glory as the only begotten of
the Father, full of grace and truth. And
he was born not of uh by mankind, which
is flesh and blood, but
of the will of God. So, that's how the
angel brought it, the body, placed it
inside, not laid with Mary, placed it
inside her womb, and she went her nine
for nine months, and then Jesus was born
because a body had to be
uh was prepared for him from the Father.
That's all I got.
All right. Thank you for that. As we
move on to our next question.
Next question, Vincent Harris asks, "Is
it a sin to exercise on the Sabbath
day?"
You should not be exercising on the
Sabbath day.
Six days may work be done, but on the
seventh day is a Sabbath of the Lord thy
God. Go to Isaiah 58. Yes, sir. Yes.
You can work out six days,
but on that Sabbath day, rest with your
Lord.
Verse 13.
If thou turn away thy foot from the
Sabbath, from doing thy pleasure on mine
holy day, and call the Sabbath a
delight, the holy of the Lord,
honorable, and shalt honor him, not
doing thine own ways, nor finding thine
own pleasure, nor speaking thine own
words. The Lord don't want you doing
your own ways or your own pleasures on
that day. He wants you to rest and give
your full thought and time to him.
Go ahead.
Then shalt thou delight thyself in the
Lord, and I will cause thee to ride upon
the high places of the earth, and feed
thee with the heritage of Jacob thy
father, for the mouth of the Lord has
spoken it. That's it. So, yeah.
No, you shouldn't be exercising on the
Sabbath day. Put Planet Fitness and LA
Fitness and your home gym and all that
aside on the Lord's Sabbath day and put
him first. And you can work out six days
a week if you like, but not on the
Lord's Sabbath day.
And that's all I got.
And Sister Deborah, can we take a
journey into new territory? New
territories.
Uh we are now into tonight's Q&A for
Wednesday, December the 10th, 2025.
Shanquilla Akujo B asks,
"Are there any verses or advice for
teenager who keeps getting into trouble
despite their families' regular
discussions of the word and attends
Sabbath classes? Are the parents doing
something wrong?"
All right. Let's open this question up
to the panel.
Let's go Let's go to Ezekiel the 18th
chapter.
He keeps He said he keeps getting into
trouble.
>> [clears throat]
>> Ezekiel the 18th chapter.
I want you to go to verse 14.
Ezekiel 18 and verse 14 says,
>> I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Verse 10.
Verse 10. Ezekiel 18 and 10. What the
book say?
If he be got a son that is a robber,
a shedder of blood, and that doeth the
like to any one of these things, Uh-huh.
and that doeth not any of those duties,
but even have eaten upon the mountains
and defiled his neighbor's wife,
have oppressed the poor and needy,
has spoiled by violence, has not
restored the pledge, and had lifted up
his eyes to the idols, have committed
abomination.
Keep going.
Have given forth upon usury, and have
taken increase. Shall he then live?
He shall not live.
He hath done all these abominations.
He shall surely die. His blood shall be
upon him.
Man. Man.
So,
that's the That's what the book say,
unless he repents.
And let him know that the wages of sin
is death.
Yes.
>> go
We need to read that scripture to him.
Where you need to go to is with him
Uh somebody find a scripture where they
come out mocking Elisha.
Yeah. And see what they all did.
I think that was a huge
These people got to know
that they even children if they keep
being unruly, the Lord would allow stuff
to happen to them.
Yeah.
Second Kings No.
Second Kings the second chapter.
Second Kings the second chapter. 23:24.
23:24. Thank you, Dre. Yeah.
So, Second Kings the second chapter
verses 23 and 24 says,
"And he went up from thence unto Bethel.
And as he was going up by the way, they
came forth little children out of the
city and mocked him and said unto him,
'Go up, thou bald head. Go up, thou bald
head.'
And he turned back and looked on them
and cursed them in the name of the Lord.
And there came forth two she bears out
of the wood and tare 40 and two children
of them."
Now, that he is the prophet Elisha.
These children come out there mocking
him and disrespecting this old prophet.
Oh, I grew up old bald head. And so, he
prayed to the Lord.
He he cursed them.
And
two female bears come down and killed 40
of them.
So, maybe somebody need to read this to
their teenage son that keeps getting in
trouble. Eventually, the Lord's going to
He's going to cross the line, and the
Lord's going to deal with him like them
she bears dealt with them kids.
That's all I got to say.
Yeah, cuz it's even in the commandments
that Exodus 20, that James read earlier,
"Honor thy father and thy mother, that
thy days may be long
upon the land which the Lord thy God
giveth thee."
Romans 6:23, "The wages of sin is
death." Can we go one Can we go to one
other place? Let's go to Proverbs 23
and read uh
read verse 13.
13 and 14.
Proverbs 23 and verse 13 and 14? Yes,
sir.
It says, "Withhold not correction from
the child.
For if thou beatest him with the rod, he
shall not die.
Thou shalt beat him with the rod and
shalt deliver his soul from hell."
Yeah, because if you don't, somebody
else will. That's right. And And you
know, Proverbs 22 and 15 Mhm. Let's read
that and that's it.
It says,
"Foolishness is bound in the heart of a
child.
But the rod of correction shall drive it
far from him."
So, don't spare that rod when it comes
to them kids.
Yeah.
Yeah, and
and if the young fellow is watching, all
of us on this panel are saying, "Cut it
out." That's right. And do what your
parents say, so that you can live the
life that God intended. Yes, sir.
All right. Let's move on to our next
question with a time check, sister.
Yes, the time is 8:55.
Jennifer Love asks, "If a person dies in
sickness, will they be raised in
sickness?"
No, they'll they'll be raised if we
talking about the first resurrection and
you talking about the second
resurrection. They're going to be raised
unto eternal life, some to everlasting
life, some to everlasting shame and
contempt. But they ain't going to be
raised with a with a sick body. They're
going to be raised with a body that, you
know, that's incorruptible.
But
and and that lake of fire
Excuse me. Go ahead.
Go to 1 Corinthians 15th chapter and
start reading. Start
>> Yeah, yeah. Verse 35.
>> [laughter]
>> Yes, sir. Okay.
Yeah, read that 35 and then I want you
to skip to verse 51 after that. Okay.
1 Corinthians 15:35
says, "But some man will say, 'How are
the dead raised up, and with what body
do they come?'" Yeah, can you read 51
and 52 for me?
It says, "Behold, I show you a mystery.
We shall not all sleep, but we shall all
be changed
in a moment, in the twinkling of an eye,
at the last trump. For the trumpet shall
sound, and the dead shall be raised
incorruptible, and we shall be changed."
But through our understanding, we know
there's a thousand years in between
that. All right, but keep reading.
Back up and read where it says
correction
and corruption.
>> 42?
Yeah.
Yeah, 42 and 43?
It says, "42 says, 'So also is the
resurrection of the dead. It is sown in
corruption.
It is raised in incorruption.
It is sown in dishonor. It is raised in
glory.
It is sown in weakness. It is raised in
power.'" Yeah, and you know, and then
you got those that's going to come up in
that second resurrection. I don't know
what kind of power they're going to
have, but their body ain't going you
know,
it ain't going to die. It ain't going to
raise be being sick, either.
Uh-uh.
All right.
Yeah, all right. Sister Deborah, time is
a ticking. Next one.
Next one. Carolyn Jenkins wants you to
explain the spirit, the water, and the
blood in 1 John 5:8.
These three are one.
Let's go there.
And open it up to the panel. 1 John
5:8.
5 and 8.
All right. Read it. 1 John 5.
Verse 8 says,
"And there are three that bear witness
in Earth, the spirit, and the water, and
the blood. And these three agree in
one."
Mhm. 1 John 6
uh uh uh
6 and 63.
Okay.
John 6 and 63? 63.
John 6 and 63 says,
"It is the spirit that quickeneth.
The flesh profiteth nothing. The words
that I speak unto you, they are spirit,
and they are life."
That's the word of God is the spirit.
And then the next is the baptism. Can
somebody go read that where you have to
be baptized?
>> [clears throat]
>> What is that? Peter?
Acts 2 and 38.
>> Acts. I'm sorry. Thanks, Dre.
Acts 2.
Yeah.
Okay.
Acts 2 and 38 says,
"Then Peter said unto them, 'Repent, and
be baptized every one of you in the name
of Jesus Christ for the remission of
sins.
And you shall receive the gift of the
Holy Ghost.
Who now? Word of the spirit? In the
baptism, you got to have water baptism?
And then as far as the
the blood is
blood
Go to Zechariah 9 and read verse 11.
9 first and then skip to verse 9 and 9
and skip down to verse 11.
Okay. Zechariah 9 and 9 says
rejoice greatly, O daughter of Zion.
Shout, O daughter of Jerusalem.
Behold, thy king cometh unto thee. He is
just and having salvation. Lowly and
riding upon an ass and upon a colt, the
foal of an ass.
Verse 11.
As for thee also, by the blood of thy
covenant, I have sent forth the
prisoners out of the pit wherein is no
water.
So, the blood is the blood of Jesus.
So, you have to First, you have to be
born of the spirit. And that way
in this particular case, you have to
The spirit is the word of God.
Then you got to be baptized.
And then you got to come under the blood
of Jesus.
And those three
are one and they and they coincide as
one.
You got to have all of them. Cuz if you
ain't got the word, then you ain't going
to be You don't know nothing about
God to be baptized.
So, once you learn it, then you got to
get baptized.
And once you get baptized, then you are
under the blood of Jesus because you are
under the new covenant.
Yes.
>> That is a
a good question to end our session on
with a time check.
The time is 9:01.
All right. Well, we have ran out of
time.
And we want to say thank you all from
all around the world who tuned in with
us. And if you sent us a question and we
didn't have time to get to it, don't
resubmit that question. Sister Deborah
take it, put it in rotation, and we will
deal with that question next week.
So, until we all come together again, we
say be safe. Be blessed. Stay prayed up.
And may the Lord have mercy on us all as
brother James closes us out.
Our Father, which art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come. Thy will be done in
earth as it is in heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread and
forgive us our debts as we forgive our
debtors.
And lead us not into temptation, but
deliver us from evil, for thine is the
kingdom and the power and the glory
forever. In Jesus' name we pray. Amen.
Amen. Amen. Good night, all. Good night,
everyone.
>> So,
um I would like to wish everybody also a
good night.
And um looks like we'll be signing
ourselves off. Good night. Good night,
everybody.
Good night.
>> Yes.
>> Hey.